The main hero finds a mythical sword in the woods and is cursed by it. The curse compels him to wander the lands and help those in need for 50 years. The King’s evil councellor wants to take the sword for himself and undermine the hero’s reputation. The King is deceived by his evil councellor and orders the main hero to be hunted down. However, the main hero saves the King’s people from the invading forces and reveals the evil councellor’s plot. The King apologizes greatly, orders the councellor to be executed, and blesses the marriage of the main hero and his love interest.